He's Setting Sail On The High Seas... Without A Rudder, A Compass, Or A Clue!
Cabin Boy is a comedy, fantasy, adventure film directed by Adam Resnick.
A foul-mouthed finishing school graduate mistakenly winds up on an ill-fated
fishing boat, and faces the wrath of a crew that considers him bad luck.
Nathanial Mayweather, played by Chris Elliott.
Captain Graybar, played by Ritch Brinkley.
Paps, played by James Gammon.
Skunk, played by Brian Doyle-Murray.
Big Teddy, played by Brion James.
Trina, played by Melora Walters.
Cabin Boy is a 1994 American fantasy comedy film directed by Adam Resnick,
co-produced by Tim Burton, and starring comedian Chris Elliott.
Elliott co-wrote the film with Resnick.
Both Elliott and Resnick worked for Late Night with David Letterman in the 1980s as
well as co-creating the Fox sitcom Get a Life in the early 1990s.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.